eurovps.com 2018-09-10

# Privacy Policy - EuroVPS

## Your Rights Under GDPR

If you are a resident of the European Economic Area, you have the following data protection rights:

If you wish to access, correct, update, or request the deletion of your personal information, you can do so at any time by emailing administration@eurovps.com. Also, you can object to the processing of your personal information, ask us to limit the processing of your personal information, or the transfer of your personal information by emailing administration@eurovps.com.

You have the right to opt-out of marketing communications we send you at any time. You can exercise this right by clicking on the "unsubscribe" or other similar "opt-out" links in the marketing materials we send you. You can also inform us that you wish to opt-out of marketing communications by emailing administration@eurovps.com.

You can withdraw your consent to our collecting and processing of your personal information at any time. Withdrawing your consent will not affect the lawfulness of any processing we conducted prior to your withdrawal, nor will it affect the processing of your personal information conducted in reliance on lawful processing grounds other than consent. 

If you’re unhappy with our collection and use of your personal information, you can complain to a data protection authority. For more information, please contact your local data protection authority.

## Vistor Data

EuroVPS may gather information from your web site visit for further analyzing. This data, assists us to customize products, and content, as well as create a more streamlined browsing experience. In pursuit of full transparency with our users, this privacy policy declares that we may track visitor IP addresses, as well as use cookie identifiers and web beacons upon visits. This is done to diagnose problems with our servers, administer our websites, recognize details of visits, target web content to users, avoid users viewing repeat content, and generally, to improve the effectiveness of our websites' content and flow.

## Information Provided By You

  1. When you register for an Account, we may ask for your contact information, including items such as name, company name, address, email address, and telephone number.
  2. When you add your financial account information to your Account, that information is directed to our third-party payment processor.
  3. If we ask you to provide us with personal information, we will always tell you why we are asking for that information. In general, when we do ask you for information, it is to verify your identity for purchases, and customer services such as account maintenance and technical support.
  4. If you contact us directly, we may receive additional information about you such as your name, email address, phone number, the contents of the message and/or attachments you may send us, and any other information you may choose to provide.

If we ask you to provide us with personal information, we will always tell you why we are asking for that information. In general, when we do ask you for information, it is to verify your identity for purchases, and customer services such as account maintenance and technical support.

## Client Web Visit

There are a number of methods of approach to EuroVPS's website that are considered a "visit." This includes utilizing a web browser that delivers you to http://www.eurovps.com; my.eurovps.com; and any other site for which the previous URL's can be considered a "root" to as well as any other sites that are owned by EuroVPS. This may also include viewing an email that has content delivered from one of our servers (or a third party web server), or by viewing an advertisement displayed on a third party website that has content delivered by one of our web servers. When web visits occur, our server may log the time/duration of your visit as well as the pages you visited on this site and the time/duration spent on them. If your arrival results from a sponsored link, paid advertisement or paid search result, statistics will be gathered from your visit. In any other event you may visit the sites represented above, information may also be gathered based on where your visit originated as well as public computer data, visible to the analysis in place. 

## Client Identifier

During your visit, a unique alphanumeric identifier may be placed on your hard drive to help us identify visitors for customization and analysis. These identifiers may also be known as "cookies" and cannot be executed as code, used to deliver a virus, be identifiable to other servers, nor can any personal information be gathered by them. EuroVPS utilizes this method solely for the aggregation of statistics used to enhance the product we offer users. If you do not want these identifiers placed upon your visit, cookies can be disabled in your web browser in the security settings that control them. It is important to note, however, that disabling cookies may hinder your ability to utilize our website at its intended performance level or to execute some functions contained in which cookies are required for security purposes. In some countries, including countries in the European Economic Area, the information referenced above in this paragraph may be considered personal information under applicable data protection laws. 

We use the information we collect in various ways, including to:

  * Provide, operate, and maintain our Services;
  * Improve, personalize, and expand our Services;
  * Understand and analyze how you use our Services;
  * Develop new products, services, features, and functionality;
  * Communicate with you, to provide you with updates and other information relating to the Service, and for marketing and promotional purposes;
  * Process your transactions;
  * Find and prevent fraud; 
  * For compliance purposes, including enforcing our Terms of Service, or other legal rights, or as may be required by applicable laws and regulations or requested by any judicial process or governmental agency.

## Web-Beacon

A small graphic known as a web beacon may be embedded into EuroVPS advertisements, emails or web pages. This is a small graphic that will result in your web browser requesting the beacon from a web server. This request results in your web browser acquiring a unique identifier that may track visitor movement on the website utilizing the web beacon. EuroVPS uses web beacons to provide customized offers and gain usage statistics that help tailor the most desired viewing experience for the majority of our visitors. No personal information is read by EuroVPS's web beacon other than raw usage statistics.

## Content

For the purpose of these Terms of Services, we define 'Content' as information and data in all forms (text, images, software, applications etc.) that is published, transmitted or otherwise stored on the hosting platform provided by EuroVPS - Including all user related content entered in the Client Portal upon registration.

## Customer Content Responsibility

Content of any form published, transmitted and stored using Services provided by EuroVPS is the full responsibility of the user/account owner. You accept that you are responsible to abide by laws, rules and regulations - any conflicting actions taken are at your own risk - and fully responsible for any damage, or loss that you may have experienced or caused to a third party as a result of your own actions.

## EuroVPS Content Responsibility

EuroVPS cannot monitor, verify, warrant, or vouch for the accuracy and quality of the information that subscribers may acquire. For this reason, the subscriber must exercise his or her best judgment in relying on information obtained from the Internet, and also should be aware that some material posted to the Internet is sexually explicit or otherwise offensive. Because EuroVPS cannot monitor or censor the Internet, and will not attempt to do so, EuroVPS cannot accept any responsibility for injury to its subscribers that results from inaccurate, unsuitable, offensive, or illegal Internet communications.

## Limitations of EuroVPS

EuroVPS does not review, edit, censor, or take responsibility for any information its subscribers may create. When users place information on the Internet, they have the same liability as other authors for copyright infringement, defamation, and other harmful speech. Subscribers' postings to the Internet may affect other subscribers and may harm EuroVPS's goodwill, business reputation, and operations. For these reasons, subscribers violate EuroVPS policy and the service agreement when they, their customers, affiliates, or subsidiaries engage in the any prohibited activities.

## EuroVPS Intervention

EuroVPS will not, as an ordinary practice, monitor the communications of its subscribers to ensure that they comply with EuroVPS policy or applicable law. When EuroVPS becomes aware of harmful activities, however, it may take any action to stop the harmful activity, including but not limited to, removing information, shutting down a web site, implementing screening software designed to block offending transmissions, denying access to the Internet, or take any other action it deems appropriate.
